I have new leggings from Slinky Styles customized latex so they may look like
latex but it's not only latex but I'm going to tell you more about everything
after I put them on all right I'd say that's a different look than before let
me tell you a bit about it so this is the leggings I'll come to that in a sec
I'm wearing an oversized latex top from shiitake with a 3d mold here and some
PVC gloves so I mixed every fabric together together with my trusty pleaser
heels I think that's a cool fetish outfit and I'm going to show you a
casual outfit afterwards let's talk about this link is 10 seconds because I
really love it. There are several specialties here. I had customized that it's higher here
up until my waist. So finally a leggings that is really high waist for me and my long body.
And I think it's a really cool look to pair it with a oversized crop top. I tried several things
also with corset but since the leggings are so high and tight here it's really cool.
Then we have a zipper and a crotch area which is perfect for going to the toilet without having
to take off the whole pants especially since it is that high and that tight.
we have the rollbeze in the back which is this huge detail and the fabric is latex so latex on
the outside fabric on the inside a special slinky style leggings you may know the pvc ones or the
leather ones but this is another variety which i really like because i like to shine and i like
that it's really comfy and easy to get into. One tip for putting these leggings on I mean
Datex is really easy to get into because of the fabric on the inside however the waistband here
is also Datex latex surface on the inside so for putting it on I just flapped it around and turned
it inside out so the Datex outside is not in contact with my skin and that made it really easy
and even if you cannot tell from the video or the pictures it is really firm
waistband and you have really have to pull a lot but once you put it on and
once it's in place it's really really cool and it really stays where it should
stay and it makes a great figure leave a thumbs up for the fetish outfit and I'm
going to switch into the street style everyday outfit now so see you in a sec
I call this look I go to a behemoth concert because I'm wearing a behemoth
t-shirt and a jacket I can take on and off if it's cold or not and comfy shoes
and still really super comfy shiny key piece of the outfit still again so this
This is my Scrooge's Day look.
Shoes are making a lot of noise.
And also the jacket is a really loud outfit, so go to a loud concert with it.
And I really love it, because I just like this band and this t-shirt and this look with
the leather jacket and the leggings and everything about it.
Of course it's something completely different than the previous outfit.
Just from the hair.
Here are the leggings.
Has to be minus blue.
Of course you can also not shine the leggings up, because I used latex shiner to make it nice and shiny.
But you can also powder it and wear it as a matte version.
But I think the fun is really in the shine of the leggings.
And if you really want a reference I had 4cm added to the waist area here. Like 4cm here, wherever. So it's a really high waist version. And you can totally customize the Flinky Stats leggings.
just have a look at the homepage I'm going to link under the video and leave a comment tell me
if you have anything made of datex or what do you think about the material I have also other
datex latex datex latex why do I say datex latex today I have other datex videos on my channel
if you want to know more about the material you can check them out and it's getting really warm
I'm wishing you a nice day and I hope you had fun. See you in the next video. Bye!